Guide to the Edwin H. Armstrong papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series IV: Alphabetical Files, 1886-1980
  - Patents
    - Application submitted by NBC to the United States Government for a High Frequency Broadcast Station Permit, 1939 July 13 (Box 129, Folder 44)
    - RCA Docket 8799--Letter to Mr. Martin Describing Noise Reduction Invention, 1934 May 23 (Box 129, Folder 45)
    - “Important FM Records”
      - Record of Discovery Notebook Detailing Experiments Taking Place on November 27, 1920 and May 10, 1933, 1920-1933 (Box 129, Folder 46)
      - Documents Relating to “Important M. Records” File, 1932-1943 (Box 129, Folder 47)
      - Photographs of John Thompson, Maurice Willey, Willie Biron, and Alpine Radio Station, 1940, undated (Box 129, Folder 48)
      - Disclosures, undated (Box 129, Folder 49)
    - “High Power File”
      - Correspondence
        - Godley, Paul to Armstrong Regarding Consultation Services, 1936-1937 (Box 130, Folder 1)
        - RCA to Armstrong Regarding Model AVT-1 Radio Traffic Control Transmitter--Includes Blueprints, 1936-1938 (Box 130, Folder 2)
        - Law Offices of Horace L. Lohnes, to Armstrong Regarding 140 foot Antenna, 1937 (Box 130, Folder 3)
        - John E. Lingo and Sons Inc. and Armstrong Regarding the Purchase, Installation and Specifications of Turnstile Antennas at Alpine--Includes Blueprints, 1937-1942 (Box 130, Folder 4)
        - Rockland Electric to Armstrong Regarding Service--Includes agreement, 1942--Usage and Tax Exemption Proposal Documents, 1937-1942 (Box 130, Folder 5)
        - Correspondence, 1937-1938 (Box 130, Folder 6)
      - Parts Lists for Armstrong Transmitter, 1938 January 26 (Box 130, Folder 7)
      - Blueprints, 1935-1937 (Box 130, Folder 8)
      - Records of Disturbance for W2XMN and WQXR, 1938-1939 (Box 130, Folder 9)
      - Westinghouse Products, 1936-1938 (Box 130, Folder 10)
      - Co-Axial Transmission Line, 1937 (Box 130, Folder 11)
      - Drawings and Notes--Original Drawings, undated (Box 130, Folder 12)
      - Notes on Radio Coverage in the Los Angeles and San Francisco Bay Area--Includes Correspondence, 1937 (Box 130, Folder 13)
    - “Early Notes, Test and Patent Specifications”
      - Original Drawings, 1932-1939 (Box 130, Folder 14)
        - Drawing, undated (Box 130, Folder 15)
      - Columbia University Announcement Concerning Armstrong’s Test of FM Radio at the Empire State Building, 1935 April 25 (Box 130, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence
        - Nolte, A.C. and Armstrong Regarding Patent Disclosures, 1932-1936 (Box 130, Folder 17)
        - President of Stern and Company to E. A Tracey, 1939 April 18 (Box 130, Folder 18)
      - Armstrong, System for Differentiating between a Single Frequency and a Varying Frequency without the Production of Transient Oscillations--Handwritten with Original Drawings, 1943 (Box 130, Folder 19)
    - “Foreign Licenses, Broadcast Transmitters Manufacturing”
      - Correspondence, 1935-1948, (3 Folders) (Box 130, Folder 20-22)
      - Maps and Photographs Concerning Coverage in Buenos Aires, Argentina, circa 1941 (Box 130, Folder 23)
      - Canadian Correspondence, 1938-1947, (2 Folders) (Box 130, Folder 24-25)
      - Canadian Radio License Agreement, 1940 January 1 (Box 130, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence
      - Regenerative Transmitter Ranges --Includes QSL Cards and Photographs, 1926 (Box 130, Folder 27)
      - United States War Department, 1942-1943 (Box 130, Folder 28)
      - Bird, Lionel Thomas to Armstrong Regarding Patent Dispute, 1945-1947 (Box 130, Folder 29)
      - Air Materiel Command--Includes Contract, 1946-1948 (Box 130, Folder 30)
    - Publications Noting Awards Given to Armstrong, 1940-1951 (Box 130, Folder 31)
    - Alpine, New Jersey--Stations W2XMN and KE2XCC
      - Confirm Receipt of Transmission Cards--QSL Cards, 1925-1926 (Box 130, Folder 32)
      - Discontinuation of Low Band W2XMN, 1949 (Box 130, Folder 33)
      - General Correspondence, 1949-1950 (Box 130, Folder 34)
      - Transmission Conditions, 1949-1950 (Box 130, Folder 35)
      - Symphony Hour, 1949-1950, (2 Folders) (Box 130, Folder 36-37)
      - Programming Correspondence, 1942-1944 (Box 130, Folder 38)
      - Bills for Programming, undated (Box 130, Folder 39)
    - Armstrong, Signaling System, 1922 (Box 130, Folder 40)
    - Non-Armstrong Patents, 1893-1920 (Box 130, Folder 41)
    - “Shaughnessy’s Notes” on De Forest v. Armstrong Case, 1921 (Box 130, Folder 42)
    - Exhibits, 1949 (Box 130, Folder 43)
    - Legal Documents Concerning Settlements, 1953 (Box 130, Folder 44)
    - Charts and Graphs, 1939 (Box 130, Folder 45)
    - Signal Testing Note Cards, undated (Box 130, Folder 46)
    - Photographs of Sine and Square Waves, 1951 (Box 130, Folder 47)
    - Photographs of Radio Equipment, undated (Box 130, Folder 48)
    - RCA Transmitter Specifications, 1940s (Box 130, Folder 49)
    - RCA Correspondence, 1936 (Box 130, Folder 50)
    - Westinghouse Correspondence, 1936 (Box 130, Folder 51)
    - Agreement between Armstrong and C.M. Jansky Jr., 1944 (Box 130, Folder 52)
    - “Notes and Abstracts of Past Examinations and Cross-Examinations of RCA Witnesses”
      - Handwritten Notes, circa 1953 (Box 131, Folder 1)
      - Memoranda, 1950-1953 (Box 131, Folder 2)
      - Testimony Notes--Handwritten Drawings and Notes, circa 1953, (2 Folders) (Box 131, Folder 3-4)
      - Documents--General, circa 1953 (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - Legal Fees to Moses and Nolte--Case Numbers and Details, 1938-1943 (Box 131, Folder 6)
    - Household Bills and Receipts
      - Stocks--Armstrong, Esther Marion, 1924-1926 (Box 131, Folder 7)
      - Telephone, 1941 and 1946 (Box 131, Folder 8)
      - General, 1941-1950 (Box 131, Folder 9)
      - Hotels, 1947-1953 (Box 131, Folder 10)
    - Household Ledger, 1939, 1943 (Box 131, Folder 11)
    - Tax Memoranda, 1937 (Box 131, Folder 12)
    - Radio Related Bills, 1931 (Box 131, Folder 13)
    - United States Patent Reprints
      - A through W, 1920s-1950s, (7 Folders) (Box 131, Folder 14-20)
    - “Patent and Patent Specifications--Diversity Systems”--Original Drawings, Notes and Annotations, circa 1952 (Box 131, Folder 21)
    - United States Geological Survey Maps--New Hampshire and New York, 1927-1934 (Box 131, Folder 22)
    - Charts, Handwritten Drawings, and Notes, 1929-1937, undated (Box 131, Folder 23)
    - Invitation to the 100th Anniversary of the United States Patent, 1936 November 23 (Box 131, Folder 24)
  - Pattison, D.R.--"Field Testing a Microwave Channel for Voice Communication, Relaying, Telemetering and Supervisory Control"--AIEE Technical Paper, 1950 April (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Penn-Allen Broadcasting Co.--Correspondence, 1947-1951 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Pennsylvania Turnpike Police Radio Installation, 1941 September (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Personalities in Science--Armstrong--Scientific American, 1943 June (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Personnel--Correspondence, Memoranda, 1948-1954 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Employment Record Cards, circa 1955 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Peters, R.G.--FM Ratio Detectors, 1945 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Peterson, Chester P.--Correspondence (photocopies), 1948 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Peterson, E.--Frequency Detection and Speech Formants, 1950 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Philco Corporation--Advertisements, 1948 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Philco Corporation Litigation
    - Armstrong v. Philco Corporation
      - Correspondence, Memoranda, Publications and Notes, 1941-1948, (2 Folders) (Box 90, Folder 11-12)
      - Pleadings, 1956 (Box 90, Folder 13)
      - Data for Suit, Extra Copies, Papers Not Used, 1942-1955 (Box 90, Folder 14)
      - Suits Against Other Infringers, 1953 (Box 90, Folder 15)
      - Philco Radio Models--Specifications, undated (Box 90, Folder 16)
      - Philco Home Radio Yearbook, 1950 (Box 90, Folder 17)
      - Philco Television Yearbook, 1949-1950, (2 Folders) (Box 90, Folder 18-19)
      - FM (Pre-war--Fake FM Sets--Correspondence, Memoranda, Advertisements, 1941-1943 (Box 90, Folder 20)
      - FM-Post War--Correspondence, Clippings, 1945-1948 (Box 90, Folder 21)
      - Infringement Circuit Diagrams, 1946, undated (Box 90, Folder 22)
      - Litigation Matters, 1944-1946 (Box 90, Folder 23)
      - Licensing, 1936-1946 (Box 90, Folder 24)
      - Philco Engineering and Equipment Data, 1944-1953, undated (Box 90, Folder 25)
      - General, 1949-1951 (Box 90, Folder 26)
      - Opinion on '069 Patent--Fish Richardson to RCA, 1939 (Box 90, Folder 27)
      - Confidential Documents, undated (Box 90, Folder 28)
      - Early FM Work, undated (Box 90, Folder 29)
      - Correspondence and Reports Regarding Armstrong Situation, 1941-1955 (Box 90, Folder 30)
      - Instruction Manual--R-F Signal Generator Model 7070, undated (Box 90, Folder 31)
      - Instruction Manual--FM and AM Signal Generator Model 7170, undated (Box 90, Folder 32)
      - Instruction and Service Manual Model 7008, undated (Box 90, Folder 33)
      - Report on RCA's Ratio Detector as Filed with SEC, 1946 (Box 91, Folder 1)
      - Newspaper and Magazine Advertisements, 1941, undated (Box 91, Folder 2)
      - Charts, undated (Box 91, Folder 3)
      - McCormack Memo "Consumer's Union" Report on Philco, 1941 (Box 91, Folder 4)
      - Philco Memo Regarding FM and Recommendation to Pool Patents, 1942 (Box 91, Folder 5)
      - Notes on Infringements, 1948 (Box 91, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence and Releases, 1939-1941 (Box 91, Folder 7)
      - Original SEC File of Exhibit 17-L From Philco Corporation on "Report on the RCA Ratio Detector," 1945 September 25 (Box 91, Folder 8)
      - Memoranda, 1953 (Box 91, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence File, 1953 (Box 91, Folder 10)
      - Legal Documents--Duplicates, 1954 (Box 91, Folder 11)
      - Legal Documents, 1953 (Box 91, Folder 12)
      - Esther Marion Armstrong v. Philharmonic Radio and Television Corp.--Pleadings, 1955 (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - Phillips Transmitting News, 1934-1935 (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - Phillips, Edward C.--Testimony of--FCC Docket No. 8487 1947 November 20 (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - Phillips, Mrs. J.F.--Correspondence, 1953 (Box 91, Folder 16)
  - Pieracci, R.J.--"A Frequency Modulation Monitoring System," 1940 (Box 91, Folder 17)
  - Phonevision--Correspondence, Clippings, Publications--Includes Armstrong's "Phonevision Idea," 1933-1953 (Box 91, Folder 18)
  - Photostats
    - Alphabetical
      - A, 1930-1957, undated, (3 Folders) (Box 134, Folder 1-3)
      - A through C,1933-1957, (3 Folders) (Box 134, Folder 4-6)
      - D through E,1930-1951 undated (Box 134, Folder 7)
      - F, 1936-1951, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 134, Folder 8-9)
      - G through H, 1943-1951, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 134, Folder 10-11)
      - I through L, 1935-1951, undated (Box 134, Folder 12)
      - M through P, 1925-1953, undated (Box 134, Folder 13)
      - R through S, 1933,-1953 undated, (4 Folders) (Box 135, Folder 1-4)
      - T through Z, 1913-1953 (Box 135, Folder 5)
    - Chronological
      - 1891-1948, (7 Folders) (Box 30, Folder 16-22)
      - 1930-1953, (10 Folders) (Box 31, Folder 1-10)
      - 1915-1925 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Uncatalogued Documents
      - Correspondence found in Lab “Carbon Copy” file, 1936-1945, (2 Folders) (Box 135, Folder 6-7)
  - Pierce, J.R. and A.L. Hopper--"Non-Synchronous Pulse Multiplex System with Random Sampling," undated (Box 91, Folder 19)
  - Pinkerton, D.C. and N.H. Shepherd--"Reducing Unwanted Radiation in Mobile Transmitters," 1950 (Box 91, Folder 20)
  - Plummer, Curtis B.--Clippings, 1950 (Box 91, Folder 21)
  - Plump, E.H.--"Interference Reduction Through Frequency Modulation," 1938-1953 (Box 91, Folder 22)
  - Pollack, Dale
    - Correspondence, 1947-1951 (Box 91, Folder 23)
    - "Interference Between Stations in Frequency Modulation Systems," 1933-1935 (Box 91, Folder 24)
    - "Comparison of Ferns Model 18C and Measurements Corporation Model 80 Signal Generators," 1948 March 8 (Box 91, Folder 25)
    - "The Design Inductances for Frequencies Between 4 and 25 Megacycles," 1937 (Box 91, Folder 26)
  - Porter, Paul--FCC Reports and Testimony, 1940-1946 (Box 91, Folder 27)
  - Popov, Alexander S.--Article in Wireless Engineer, 1949 August (Box 91, Folder 28)
  - Preece, W.H.--"Signaling Through Space Without Wires," 1897 (Box 91, Folder 29)
  - Pratt, H.--'The First Fifty Years of International Radio Communication', 1952 (Box 91, Folder 30)
  - Press Wireless, Inc.--Correspondence, 1951 (Box 91, Folder 31)
  - Price, Pattie--Correspondence, 1948-1952 (Box 91, Folder 32)
  - Priest, Conan A.--Publications, 1946-1949 (Box 91, Folder 33)
  - Production--Production of FM Sets in Home Receivers--Correspondence, Memoranda, Charts, Publications, 1950-1953 (Box 91, Folder 34)
  - Promotion--Publications, Correspondence, 1950 (Box 91, Folder 35)
  - Propaganda--Hostile--Includes the United Kingdom, 1930-1953 (Box 91, Folder 36)
  - Propagation--Ionospheric Radio Propagation--Publications, Reports, Correspondence, 1948-1950, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 91, Folder 37-38)
  - Radiation--Oscillator Radiation Field Checks--Article, 1950, undated (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Radio and Television, Inc. Litigation
    - Armstrong v. Radio and Television, Inc.
      - Pleadings, 1956 (Box 92, Folder 2)
      - Data, Extra Copies, Papers Not Used, 1955 (Box 92, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, 1955 (Box 92, Folder 4)
      - Legal Documents, 1956 (Box 92, Folder 5)
      - Charts, 1957, undated (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - QST: A Magazine Devoted Entirely to Amateur Radio
    - Schnell Expedition, 1925 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Editorial on March 1940 FCC Hearings on FM, 1940 May (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Editorial Salute to Edwin H. Armstrong, undated (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Articles, 1950-1952 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Pupin, Michael
    - Correspondence, Articles, 1895-1950 (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Graphs, Blueprints--Half-Lengths For Various Frequencies, 1918 (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Radar--Correspondence--Includes Notes and Drawings Regarding Guided Missiles Radar, 1946-1947 (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - Public Relations--"Armstrong Personal"--Correspondence, Invoices, Articles, 1939-1948 (Box 92, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence Between Armstrong and Public Relations Firms, 1940-1948 (Box 92, Folder 15)
  - Radio
    - The Armstrong System Trademark, undated (Box 92, Folder 16)
    - Publications, Advertisements, Articles and Programs--Includes Wireless Map, 1910-1980, undated, (10 Folders) (Box 92, Folder 17-26)
    - Publications--Includes Early Catalogs of De Forest Radio Telephone and Telegraph Co.--Telefunken--Marconi Wireless Telegraph Company, Ltd., 1903-1953, undated, (9 Folders) (Box 223, Folder 1-9)
    - Programs, Conferences, Awards and Banquets, 1916, 1930-1940 (Box 92, Folder 27)
  - The Radio Club of America, Inc.
    - Proceedings of the, 1919-1922, 1934-1947, 1948-1958, (3 Folders) (Box 93, Folder 1-3)
      - "The Legacies of Edwin Howard Armstrong" volume 64, number 3, 1990 November (Box 262, Folder 8)
    - 41st Anniversary Banquet, 1950 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - 43rd Anniversary Banquet and Presentation of the Armstrong Medal to H.J. Round, 1952 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - 44th Anniversary Banquet and Presentation of the Armstrong Medal to Raymond Heising, 1953 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Publications and Newsletters, 1963-1972, (2 Folders) (Box 93, Folder 7-8)
    - Correspondence, Papers, Drafts, Meeting Minutes and Nominations, 1948-1953, (3 Folders) (Box 93, Folder 9-11)
    - Photographs--Includes Dedication Ceremonies of 1BCG Monument, Edwin H. Armstrong, George E. Burghard, Paul Godley and Ernest V. Amy, Greenwich, Connecticut, 1950 October 21 (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - Lecture Notes Before the Radio Club--FM Paper with Multiplex, undated (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - Technical Paper--"Some Recent Developments in the Multiplexed Transmission of Frequency Modulated Broadcast Signals"--Drafts and Figures, Includes Photograph, 1953 (Box 247 (flat), Folder 2)
  - RCA Litigation
    - Armstrong v. RCA and NBC
      - Publications, Memoranda, Correspondence, Press Releases, Blueprints and Reports, 1931-1950, (2 Folders) (Box 93, Folder 14-15)
      - Armstrong Frequency Modulation Receivers--Technical Report by G.L. Beers, 1935 (Box 93, Folder 16)
      - H.H. Beverage Letter to FCC enclosing Curves of 45.1 Mc Recordings Made at Riverhead by Peterson, 1945 (Box 93, Folder 17)
      - Burrell's Field Tests of Wideband FM and AM From Empire State Transmitter, 1934-1935 (Box 93, Folder 18)
      - Circuit Diagrams and Technical Paper Information, 1946-1947 (Box 93, Folder 19)
      - Equipment, Other Than Receivers, 1947 (Box 93, Folder 20)
      - Financial Information and Data, 1945-1946, undated (Box 93, Folder 21)
      - Frequency Modulation--Report, 1939 December (Box 93, Folder 22)
      - "Frequency Modulation Distortion Caused by Multipath Transmission, TR821,"--Corrington, 1942 November 12 (Box 93, Folder 23)
      - Infringement and Litigation Matters--Correspondence and Legal Documents, 1929-1954 (Box 93, Folder 24)
      - RCA Publications and Press Releases, 1930-1950 (Box 93, Folder 25)
      - Sadenwater Reports, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1933-1947 (Box 93, Folder 26)
      - "Simultaneous Field Strength Recordings on 47.1, 106.5 and 700 Mc, PTR-55"--W.L. Carlson, 1946 October 2 (Box 93, Folder 27)
      - Oman's "A New Exciter Unit for Frequency Modulation Transmitters," 1946 November (Box 93, Folder 28)
      - "Simultaneous Field Strength Recordings on 46.7, 83.76 and 103 Mc, PTR-31"--W.L. Carlson, 1945 November 9 (Box 93, Folder 29)
      - Technical--"V" Antenna--Blueprints, 1929 (Box 95, Folder 1)
      - FM Receivers--Clippings and Correspondence, 1946-1947 (Box 95, Folder 2)
      - Suggestions and Help in Infringement Against RCA--Correspondence, 1939-1948 (Box 95, Folder 3)
      - Television--Clippings and Advertisements, 1935-1951 (Box 95, Folder 4)
        - General, 1932-1951 (Box 95, Folder 5)
      - Neinburger Report, 1941 (Box 95, Folder 6)
      - Testimony Before FCC--Beverage and Schairer, 1950 (Box 95, Folder 7)
      - Sarnoff File--General, 1950-1952 (Box 95, Folder 8)
      - Tunick Testimony--Notes, 1952 (Box 95, Folder 9)
      - Notes for Examination of Black, 1952 (Box 95, Folder 10)
      - Abstract's of Hanson's Testimony on Listening to Alpine, 1952 (Box 95, Folder 11)
      - Letter Summaries, 1948 (Box 95, Folder 12)
      - Summary Statement and Conclusions Concerning FCC TID, 1949 (Box 95, Folder 13)
      - 1940 Disclosure of RCA's Actions in 1932 Anti-Trust Suit, 1940-1942 (Box 95, Folder 14)
      - Armstrong's Cross Examination Notes, undated (Box 95, Folder 15)
      - Morris, Carbon, Clements and Hathaway--Notes, 1952 (Box 95, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence, 1914-1934 (Box 95, Folder 17)
      - Pollack Testimony--Notes, undated (Box 95, Folder 18)
      - Dome Testimony--Notes, 1953 (Box 95, Folder 19)
      - Notes from Labus-Priest Report, 19301-947 (Box 95, Folder 20)
      - "General Research" and "Television Research"--RCA Reports, 1933 (Box 95, Folder 21)
      - Articles and Crosby Notes, 1923-1950 (Box 95, Folder 22)
      - Wide Swing Patent--Information Obtained by Questioning Armstrong and Notes, 1948 (Box 95, Folder 23)
      - Memoranda and Testimony, 1952 (Box 95, Folder 24)
      - General Correspondence, 1931-1934 (Box 95, Folder 25)
      - References to Adversely Held Patents, 1939-1943 (Box 95, Folder 26)
      - General, 1930-1931 (Box 95, Folder 27)
      - "Frequency Modulation"--RCA, 1939 (Box 95, Folder 28)
      - "Proposed Plan for Television"--RCA, 1933 (Box 95, Folder 29)
      - "New Approaches to Broadcasting"--RCA, undated (Box 95, Folder 30)
      - "A Study Made by the Engineering Department of Early Commercialization of Research and Development Projects in the Field of Special Apparatus"--RCA, 1939 (Box 95, Folder 31)
      - "A Study of the Characteristics of the Radio Detector and its Place in Radio History"--Armstrong, 1948 (Box 95, Folder 32)
      - Exhibit Statistics, 1954 (Box 95, Folder 33)
      - Armstrong Statement, 1934-1953 (Box 95, Folder 34)
      - Organization Chart, 1943 (Box 95, Folder 35)
      - RCA License, 1946 (Box 95, Folder 36)
      - Armstrong Agreements, undated (Box 95, Folder 37)
      - General, 1936-1954 (Box 95, Folder 38)
      - General, 1943-1953 (Box 96, Folder 1)
      - Sales Material, 1945 (Box 96, Folder 2)
      - Decision Circuit Court of Appeals 2nd Circuit--Correspondence, 1933-1934 (Box 96, Folder 3)
      - Awards, 1931-1942 (Box 96, Folder 4)
      - Notes for Examination of Shelby, Buzalski, Brown and Crosby, 1951-1952 (Box 96, Folder 5)
      - Notes for Examination of Schairer, 1952 (Box 96, Folder 6)
      - Notes for Examination of Sarnoff, 1953 (Box 96, Folder 7)
      - Cross-Over Characteristics from Hathaway and Crosby's Tests, 1940 (Box 96, Folder 8)
      - Notes on Dunn's Testimony, 1951 (Box 96, Folder 9)
      - Beverage Examination Notes, 1951-1952 (Box 96, Folder 10)
      - Armstrong's Testimony--Abstracts, 1953 (Box 96, Folder 11)
      - Receivers--ACA Publicity, 1944 (Box 96, Folder 12)
      - Notes and Abstracts from Tunick's Testimony, 1952 (Box 96, Folder 13)
      - General Correspondence, 1931 (Box 96, Folder 14)
      - History of Short Wave "Professional Development" in America--Handwritten Notes, undated (Box 96, Folder 15)
      - FM Notes and Diagrams, 1931-1941 (Box 96, Folder 16)
      - Dunn Transcripts, 1939 (Box 96, Folder 17)
      - Nolte Correspondence and Disclosures, Radio Log, 1937-1952 (Box 96, Folder 18)
      - Abstracts of Tunick and Crosby Testimony, 1952 (Box 96, Folder 19)
      - Notes on Bucher Examination and Reports, 1952 (Box 96, Folder 20)
      - 1:1 Deviation--Graphs, undated (Box 96, Folder 21)
      - References to Important RCA Letters and Reports, 1939-1947 (Box 96, Folder 22)
      - Reports of Executive Committee, 1943-1944 (Box 96, Folder 23)
      - Abstracts and Copies of RCA Documents by LaPorte and Raymond, undated (Box 96, Folder 24)
      - Original Disclosure of "Phone Vision," 1933 (Box 96, Folder 25)
      - General, 1952 (Box 96, Folder 26)
      - Sadenwater's Abstracts and Notes on RCA Reports, 1939-1940 (Box 96, Folder 27)
      - Calculations Based on Sound Curves From Fletcher and Olson Used in Tunick's Testimony, undated (Box 96, Folder 28)
      - Pollack Correspondence, 1938-1945 (Box 96, Folder 29)
      - Tunick Testimony and Notes, 1952, (2 Folders) (Box 96, Folder 30-31)
      - General Notes, 1939-1944 (Box 96, Folder 32)
      - Marconi File, 1914-1922 (Box 96, Folder 33)
      - Interference--Transcript, undated (Box 96, Folder 34)
      - "Informal Address on Radio"--David Sarnoff, 1922 (Box 96, Folder 35)
      - Coordination Committee Minutes of RCA, 1929 (Box 97, Folder 1)
      - The Rule Against Patenting Natural Phenomena, undated (Box 97, Folder 2)
      - License Agreement--General, 1939-1940 (Box 97, Folder 3)
      - "Down to Earth on 'High Fidelity'," 1944 (Box 97, Folder 4)
      - Translated German Articles, 1928-1929 (Box 97, Folder 5)
      - RCA Engineering Reports on Frequency Modulation for Picture Transmission in Television, undated (Box 97, Folder 6)
      - Preliminary Meetings Considering the Wide Band System, undated (Box 97, Folder 7)
      - Reference or Reports of Meetings from Executive Grouping, undated (Box 97, Folder 8)
      - "Some Effects of Phase Distortion in the TD-2 Radio System-Case 38491"--Technical Memorandum and Notes, 1951 (Box 97, Folder 9)
      - Minutes of Meeting of the RMA Committee on FM, 1939 (Box 97, Folder 10)
      - Answers and Objections to Plaintiff's Second Interrogatories, undated (Box 97, Folder 11)
      - Clippings, 1942-1953 (Box 97, Folder 12)
      - Olson and Fletcher Articles, 1922 (Box 97, Folder 13)